{
    "id": "c3fa74d3ddb546e2a24eee8d6671ab27",
    "title": "Kinds Of Nouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The book was lying on the table.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Book is a common noun",
                "Book is a proper noun",
                "Book is a collective noun"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8a755d425a304701b6ea383cbd562d55"
        },
        {
            "question": "Love begets love.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Love is a common noun",
                "Love is a collective noun",
                "Love is an abstract noun"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fd9b39d56f80434f9a6eab15e36dd2a5"
        },
        {
            "question": "We cannot live without water.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Water is a common noun",
                "Water is a material noun",
                "Water is an abstract noun"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7239199d24f0488ca6a24a155d02ea29"
        },
        {
            "question": "The jury has given its verdict.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Jury is a collective noun",
                "Jury is a common noun",
                "Jury is an abstract noun"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d0b0f2726ec4403c83e4bade9d0ef002"
        },
        {
            "question": "The Hindus regard Krishna as an incarnation of Lord Vishnu.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Hindus is a common noun",
                "Hindus is a proper noun",
                "Hindus is an abstract noun"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e221f69b139447499841fa24ae64d4c1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Alcohol is injurious to health.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Health is a common noun",
                "Health is an abstract noun",
                "Health is a proper noun"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "194abf578c7149cdb2956ff128699523"
        },
        {
            "question": "Smoking is a bad habit.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Habit is a common noun",
                "Habit is a proper noun",
                "Habit is an abstract noun"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "000e6eae82a94bfcb796589301ca8812"
        },
        {
            "question": "Wild animals live in forests.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Animals is a common noun",
                "Animals is a proper noun",
                "Animals is an abstract noun"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7cfe55e3f4bf48fbb248697403f591ef"
        },
        {
            "question": "The childhood of Peter was full of misery.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Childhood is a common noun",
                "Childhood is an abstract noun",
                "Childhood is a proper noun"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "33c79ec58c9544378626dcaca2483682"
        },
        {
            "question": "All the girls were singing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Girls is a common noun",
                "Girls is a proper noun",
                "Girls is an abstract noun"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "43334e44481e4da583c251c0a7a8002b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Gold is a precious metal.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Gold is a proper noun",
                "Gold is an abstract noun",
                "Gold is a material noun"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "dfba98acfeee46e4a1afba0cc3570697"
        },
        {
            "question": "Rice is the staple food of South Indians.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Rice is a common noun",
                "Rice is a material noun",
                "Rice is an abstract noun"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5c85c14a73f043c4acaf7bacd16bc130"
        },
        {
            "question": "The earth moves round the sun.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Earth is a common noun",
                "Earth is an abstract noun",
                "Earth is a proper noun"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6138b19d93a0403cb532d1e5f60df2c6"
        }
    ]
}